<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>A Bl0g by the students at the Kalamazoo Area Mathematics and Science Center, Kalamazoo, Michigan.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>What to do this summer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Now that that the 2016-17 school year is over, it is time to start thinking about the summer and next school year (not before you’ve had a very relaxing and exciting summer).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For all of those interested in going to college after high school, it is never too early to start touring college campuses to find out exactly what you like. The earlier you start, the more colleges you can visit and the better you can find what you like. Even if you don’t plan on attending a college, it is always best to visit it anyways. Mr. Cardwell will talk a lot of this in IT 9th grade year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, camps are a great idea for the summer. If you are interested in attending a summer camp make sure to email Ms. Joyce about all of the wonderful opportunities for KAMSC students in any grade. She has years of experience with summer camps and other interesting events for students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to share your ideas or experiences with summer camps in the comments section below. Enjoy the summer!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/06/15/what-to-do-this-summer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/06/15/what-to-do-this-summer.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thinking About Summer?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been only four days since KAMSC got over! What have you been up to for the past few days? Have you already planned everything for Summer 2k17 yet? Or, what have you planned out already? Anything cra2y, fun, exc1ting, j0yous, awes0m3, or all of the above?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to share your ideas in the comments section below.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/06/13/summer-plans.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/06/13/summer-plans.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome! Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s going to be an amazing year with this bl0g!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are free to write anything you like on this bl0g. Just go ahead and email your content to any of the following emails: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:kamscblog@icloud.com&quot;&gt;kamscblog@icloud.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2017/06/11/welcome-post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2017/06/11/welcome-post.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
